upfront group
Here we go...it's up-cami. This time we have with us Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume '23 and Kirara Yonemura of Ocha Norma.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the upfront group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with the backstage of the two MCs.
First of all, let me introduce Yokoyama,
Speaking of recent events, we have been banned from performing live with our voices,
We Morning Musume '13 have been banned from speaking out at the Ehime concert,
We are seated audience, but we were finally allowed to speak out our voices,
At first, the fans and we were a bit confused.
We were a little confused at first, both the fans and ourselves. Or something like that,
I could see that the fans were enjoying the show with us while looking around,
I thought it was kind of cute,
I thought it was cute that they were enjoying the live performance with their voices,
I'm really looking forward to seeing more and more vocal performances in the future.
I am looking forward to seeing more and more vocal live performances in the future. We, Ocha-no-Ame, have experienced live vocal performances at outside events and so on,
The fans of Ocha-no-Ame were so energetic from the very beginning that we were really overwhelmed,
They were so loud and excited that we were really overwhelmed,
I am looking forward to seeing how the atmosphere of the live show will change depending on the group.
I, Yonemura, recently held my first birthday event,
I was quite nervous for my first birthday event, but once the event started, I had so much fun,
I was quite nervous at my first birthday event, but once the event started, I was having a lot of fun,
I am Italian red, which is the member's color, and they turned the penlights this color, and it was such a beautiful scenery,
I was so happy to think that I could make my debut and hold such a great event,
I also handed out masks of my face to everyone.
Oh, my.
It was an admission present.
Oh, a present already.
That's right.
It was like I was trying to turn everyone into Kirara Yonemura,
What a great plan.
Yes, you can do whatever you want.
It was a lot of fun and a great memory.
Birthday events really have an atmosphere that can only be found at birthday events,
It's like they are really coming to see me, and that makes me really happy.
I have a birthday every year.
Yay!
Each time, I would like to enjoy myself while planning various events.
Yes, so let's start with the thick paper this time.
Beyonds Biophonic Making Video
A special live concert with an orchestra was held on May 2 at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space,
Please take a look at the behind-the-scenes footage of the rehearsal and performance of "Beyonds Biophonic" held on May 2 at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space.
See the rehearsal.
The glowing colored sticks that everyone is holding.
And the ham cutlet.
This is our precious ham cutlet.
This is a penlight.
It says "ear fanning" here.
This is Miyons.
Good morning.
But I have a dream.
Look to the infinite limit.
Miracles will happen.
I'll soar like the wind
Let's fly, let's soar on our journey
I, the straggling voice
I wish I could give it to Nadarahancha
Haguretsukuru Sekai Haguretsukuru Reason ha-haguretsukuru
I'll be fine tomorrow, let's come again
I've had it, I've had it, I've had it, I've had it, I've had it, I've had it
It's okay, I'm here
Yes, I love you too
Oh, my God!
Yes! I'm trying to say, "Yes!" like this.
It's good.
I'll tell him you woke me up this morning.
That's not easy, is it?
The atmosphere at the rehearsal was pretty much, you know, half of the people were cosmetically normal and half of them were nervous.
I'm pretty much the same as usual.
But the orchestra was there, so the atmosphere of the music was pretty good.
The atmosphere of the music had changed to a more elegant one.
I hope you will enjoy the arrangements, which you don't usually hear at our concerts.
So I hope you will enjoy it.
Gil the irreplaceable!
Thank you for your hard work!
Mr. Oh-kun, I'm here for a snack.
Jajankenpa
Oh, kun, I'm here for a snack.
This song makes me the most nervous.
Sometimes it opens even though I didn't press the button when we have a bad match.
Or it opens up again even after it's closed.
I can't tell you how many times I've been traumatized by this.
But this time, it's a one-shot deal.
So I'm going to do my best.
If you have a dream, the battle will be fought tonight.
The door to the music opens in an instant.
I'm sorry if you go in there.
Or I'll destroy someone and we'll be out of here.
That's what I'm getting at. Swallow the milk to the ground.
It's time to paint it shine, scrape it off the ground, and then we'll get through this.
That day... that day... that day... that day...
Tomorrow.
It's too scary, but...
It's a different kind of concert with a different atmosphere and a lot of tension.
I want to enjoy it. It's a great opportunity for me.
I want to enjoy it.
Thank you for watching.
Half an orchestra!
Why did I stay quiet?Why have I been quiet?
I'm nervous.
Yesterday I said I wasn't nervous,
But when I come to the venue, I'm quite anxious.
I'd like to do it in Milanov, thank you very much.
The Boy with the Glass Bell
The boy until the day it rains
The moment when everyone is though
You and I are sharing a song
It's a miracle
Come on, now
I'm so happy
I want to be different again
Logan Elena lala lala lala lala lala
As long as I'm old enough I can do it all
Trouble Mighty Pour and pour
[Applause]
It is finally starting.
I have red as my member color,
I have red goals, and I made my hair red,
I also made my mouth very red.
The day has finally arrived.
Yay!
I am nervous,
I'm nervous, but all I can do now is to enjoy myself,
Let's have fun!
There will be a lot of guests all the way to the end,
Let's make them all go home captivated.
Let's go Beyond!
The show is over.
I could hear the applause of the audience even though I was playing earmony.
Not so much with the leaders and a few of the audience members.
In terms of time, you know.
It was too nice.
I want to do it again.
It felt good, didn't it?
Like at the last Himefest, I was told what to do right up until the last minute, "I have to do this, that, and the other,
But once I got on stage, I felt like I was transported to another world, and it was a lot of fun.
It was ah-ha!
The biophonic was successfully finished!
It was really 12 of us, and with the staff and the orchestra.
and the staff, the orchestra, and Mr. Yukuro Fuchihara.
Everyone really shined and sparkled!
We were given the opportunity to perform at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space, which is a wonderful hall.
I was able to experience the sound of the hall and the orchestra's arrangement.
I was able to finish the performance while enjoying the orchestral arrangements very much.
I also had a chance to play a lot of piano.
I also got to play a lot of piano.
I was already looking back in my head
I really had a lot of fun!
I hope everyone enjoyed the shining colors.
Please enjoy the video as well!
It was beautiful! It was beautiful!
I couldn't imagine what it would be like to have an idol and an orchestra.
But I was surprised to see how well they matched with each other.
I was so surprised! I wondered what it would be like with an orchestra.
The orchestra and the Beyonds were rehearsing together, and the Beyonds alone were thinking about the formation.
I could see them discussing with each other, and I thought it was really cool.
Project, so keep an eye on the Beyonds.
Project, so I'd like to pay more and more attention to Beyonds in the future.
I think the first thing about Beyonds is that their unison is so beautiful, just like a music hall.
Beautiful! Really beautiful!
I mean, you are like a musical instrument, like a musical instrument, like a musical instrument.
Indeed, indeed!
My ears were so happy!
Really!
And the costumes... everyone was so orchestral.
It was so cute!
It was so cute. My eyes were happy. My ears were happy.
I wish I could have seen it live.
I really wish I could have seen it.
I wish I could have seen it.
That's all for now, this is Beyonds biophonic making video.
You can do it!
Next up is Angerme's top vocal recording!
Here's a clip of Rin Kawase recording vocals for Angerme's latest album, Big Love.
Okay, let's get some footage.
Okay.
Okay, let's start with the A melody.
From "confidence is so cute" to "runway.
Okay.
Let's try it once.
Yes, please.
He's so dry with his confidence. He's so boring.
He's so scared, it's obvious. Just watch.
I'm gonna take my best steps, and this is my runway
I'm gonna make him sing like he usually sings in Hello! I have a plan to make him sing more like this, but for this song, I think he's the coolest.
But for this song, Kero thinks it's the coolest,
I think it would be best if I could sing it with confidence.
If you hear something you want to do better, please keep working on it.
I understand. Yes, there are a lot.
OK, let's try it again.
Please do.
It's obvious you're freaking out. Just watch me.
I'm going with my best step. This is my runway.
Isn't that good? Here. OK.
Okay, then that next block.
You're the one who's not sure.
Let's go dynamite from here, shall we?Let's go from here to Dynamite, shall we?
Yes, it's going to be a little bit more rhythmic here, so it probably won't be as serious as it is here.
I hope you can catch up with what you're singing now and sing well from here again.
Okay, let's go.
I don't want to be spoiled, I want to be spoiled sometimes
I want to be selfish, I want to be selfish, I want to be selfish, I want to be selfish, I want to be selfish, I want to be selfish.
I think it's totally fine to be so bossy. What's wrong with that? I think it's good that he has a "what's wrong with you?
I don't want to be spoiled sometimes
Sometimes I want to be spoiled
I want to be as selfish as I want to be
Weed dynamite for human resources
OK!
Then, let's go with Nekuru too!
Weed dynamite for your talent
Hey, I'm cool or I'm cute, I can be either, depending on my mood
I'm both front and back, so there's no problem here.
I think we can be pretty serious here.
Hey, I want to be cool or I want to be cute
I'm both, front and back, depending on how I feel.
I don't have a problem with that.
Don't say "front.
I'm just trying to figure out what to do with the "right" part.
I'm just saying that I don't really have a problem with it.
I don't have a problem with that, but I don't know if I should say "so you say" like it's a line.
I don't know, I don't know.
I think I'm going to change the take here, or change the person, or change the take, or something like that.
I don't know.
I think I'll just do this later. I think I'll just say, "I guess so" later. Yes. Sing that much. Yes. Please do.
Hey, I want to be both cool and cute, depending on my mood.
I'm both front and back. Mondaíba daíba.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's try rustling once.
Can I go on and on?
I'll put a piece on it for you.
Mondaiba daiba
I, Tok Tok Tok to Company Album Rain no Soba
I'll go to tteok tteok and...
I'll go to tteoktteok
I'll show you
I'll show you.
Just once, now.
I'll show you that I don't doubt you.
That tteok tteok sounded so good.
I'll use it now.
Just that part.
I'd like to take one test shot.
They're both smiling a little too much.
Isn't that Nico?
Neat.
Niat.
Let's sing a chorus, just for the sake of it.
Okay, I think we're done with this song.
Thank you very much.
This song is a unit song of Rikako Sasaki, Ryumoe Kamekado and Rin Kawahara.
I got the impression that it was a stylish and cool song, which is typical of Angerme.
I really like Rin Kawahara's high notes.
The way it echoes during the talk part, it's like her voice is cute and stylish at the same time.
It matched the song so well, and it made me want to hear her cheers one more time.
I think that the music is a little bit quieter than in other places.
I thought it would be difficult for her to sing, but Rin Kawahara sang so well and in such a stylish way.
I'd love to see her live performance.
That's all for now, this is the vocal recording of Rin Kawahara, the top singer of Angerme.
Let's work hard together!
Morning Musume '23's Reina Yokoyama and Kirara Yonemura from Ochanomama are here with you.
Next up, here we go! Tsubaki Factory No Mistake, No Crying Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Shigeo Akiyama from Tsubaki Factory's latest single, "No Mistake, No Cry or No Cry"!
Okay, this is the most sad and mature song in Tsubaki's history!
Yes, sir.
A little bit like that image
Yes, sir
Okay, let's give it a try.
Please do.
Let's do it.
I've been told lately that I'm getting more mature.
I'm becoming more like you. I was trying to be taller.
I'm going to sing some more.
Mumble, mumble, mumble.
As if it's all about me.
Yes, sir.
I'm getting more mature these days
I'm sure they'll say I've grown to be more like you
I'll grow up and go to the dance
I'll sing all the way to the end
Yes, sir
And be a little conscious of the rhythm
Yes, sir.
Don't be too slow.
I've been told lately that I'm getting more mature.
I'm going to be a good fit for you. I've been trying to be taller.
I've become what you want me to be.
Okay.
Wow!
Let's just take the second line, shall we?
Yeah, sure.
I bet you're the one who's been telling me I'm all grown up these days.
Okay, I got it!
Okay, B melody number one?
Yes, sir!
B-melody.[B melody]
Yeah, the last part of the shakuri, it's a little more forward.
The "give" is the same as now, "give," "give," "give," "give," "give," "give," "give.
Te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te.
It's quite difficult, isn't it? In the current version, I'm shaking my head. And I'm texturing it with "give it up.
Daritan.
You're a little slow.
Daritān.
Give it up, give it up, give it up, give it up, give it up.
It's a little harder than you might think.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Yes, yes, that's better. The propulsive force gives a sense of speed.
That's better. The propulsion makes it go faster. It's a little bit flabby.
Tee-hee! That's right. That's right.
I don't want to get angry. Give me that. CV.
I don't want to get mad, but...
Give it to me.
You're doing it live.
I might do it.
Raise it.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
It'll be fun.
I'm doing it.
That's what I mean.
Okay, let's try it again.
Can you do it? Yes, I can.
I got it.
You did it!
Yes, sir.
Let's try the first chorus then.
Raise your face
I who fell in love with you
It still hurts now
But it's not just that I lost you
The world has changed since I met you
No regrets, no love, no nothing.
I think the last image is better
The first one.
The first part. Not too much humming and hawing.
A little more restrained.
It's a little more restrained.
I think it's like expressing the high without showing too much emotion.
Also, you know,
It still hurts now, but...
I'm going to cover it up a little bit.
I'm going to cross while lowering the pitch, so I'm going to hang it a little bit.
Then, I'm going to embrace the future.
Make sure you get that part right.
I'm going to be particular about how I end the sentence.
Yes.
I didn't just lose it.
The world that began to change after meeting you
I embrace all the regrets and love in my future.
OK, let's try this.
The other side
You're not wrong.
This side is stronger
And I'm going to pile on the chorus a little bit.
Yes, sir.
And throw in the end a little bit.
No mistake, no mistake, no mistake.
"This wound is for the next season, for the next blooming season.
It's a bit cool, too.
I won't cry, I'll throw it.
I can't cry, I'm going to throw it.
I can't cry, I have to throw.
I'll give it a try.
You'll see what I mean.
Okay, take one.
Right now.
The way you throw or the way you pull out...
You pull everything out at the top, don't you? Yes.
I'd like to see a variation where you pull it out a little lower. Yes.
Now, you say you don't cry. You tend to pull it out.
But you don't cry about it.
So, pull out the "ngagu". Lower the sound.
I can't cry. You're going up now, right?
You say "no". It's not there. It's not there.
I want to be able to use it too. Yes, I do.
It's not a mistake. Yes, it is. Next time. No doubt.
This Keys also next.
I won't cry.
I can't cry.
Yes, I can. If you can use that one too, you can do a lot of variations.
If you play all of them, you get the sadness, but I don't think it fits some songs.
This time, I'm going to give it a try and see if I can get used to it.
No mistake, I'm in love with you
No mistake, it still hurts now
But this wound will bloom in the next season
I won't cry, I didn't just lose you
I can't cry about you
Here it is. We're done.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it's a very good song.
And at the same time, it's very difficult to play.
I feel like it's both very good and very difficult at the same time.
This one alone seems to be difficult.
I was listening to it while thinking it was difficult.
You have to keep the rhythm with the low notes.It's very difficult to keep the rhythm and emotion in the low notes.
It's very difficult to keep the rhythm and the emotion in the low notes.
In such a situation, it's very difficult to keep the rhythm
while breathing a little.
Akema, you did it so well.
I thought it was amazing.
I thought it was really cool.
I thought it looked really difficult, too.
from the first time I heard this song.
I thought, "What a paper song!
It's a really great song, isn't it?
It really shakes me up.
It shakes my soul
It's such a great song.
But it's really good because there are some rap parts
and rap parts in the song
I was wondering how you recorded the song
I was wondering how the song was recorded
It was a lot of fun to see what goes on behind the scenes.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory.
No mistakes, no tears
It's not a mistake, I won't cry... It was a vocal recording by Maoho Akiyama.
Angerme Ai no Kedamono June 14 On-size
You can do it
It's time to say goodbye to Rena Yokoyama and Kirara Yonemura's upsides!
I, Kirara Yonemura, was impressed by the biophonic performance.
It was so amazing, I got goosebumps just watching the video.
The music was so amazing that I really wanted to go see it live, but I was so happy to be able to see the backstage of the performance like this.
I can't forget Rin Kawana's singing voice.
I was so happy to see her singing on the back side of the stage. I'm going to go listen to it when I'm done with this up-dated paper.
I'm going to go listen to it after I'm done with this up-dated paper.
I was so happy to see the video of the recording session because I think it's really rare to see such a video.
In this issue, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
We'll be showing you what you don't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel! This time, Upsha is joined by Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume '23's Reina Yokoyama and
Kirara Yanagimura from Ochanoma.
Next time on ATSUKAMI,
Morning Musume '23 new members' lessons!
And,
Beyonds, we will show you the recording of the instrumental recording of "Yumeno Sukunna Yozora Ni Ni".
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel!
by H.